{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "English for Academic & Professional Purposes",
    "Term": "First Quarter",
    "Title": "Academic and Non-Academic Texts",
    "LastModified": "15 August 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "What are specialized, formal pieces of writing, crafted by experts within a specific field?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
        "Analytical Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is characterized by their use of objective language, evidence-based arguments, and adherence to a structured format?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Persuasive Text",
        "Descriptive Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What aims to inform, analyze, or persuade a scholarly audience, relying on research and data to support claims?",
      "answer": "Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Text",
        "Analytical Text",
        "Critical Academic Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What usually delivers simple and basic information?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Descriptive Text",
        "Social Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What can be read and easily understood by any kind of reader?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Social Language",
        "Persuasive Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is personal, emotional, impressionistic, or subjective in nature?",
      "answer": "Non-Academic Text",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Text",
        "Non-Academic Text",
        "Academic Language",
        "Critical Academic Text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Non-Academic Text Definition"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text provides facts and information?",
      "answer": "Descriptive",
      "choices": [
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Descriptive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text organizes facts and information into categories, groups, parts, types or relationships?",
      "answer": "Analytical",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text includes argument, recommendation, interpretation, or evaluation of the work of others with the addition of your own point of view?",
      "answer": "Persuasive",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text needs to be supported by evidence?",
      "answer": "Persuasive",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of academic text requires you to consider at least two points of view, including your own?",
      "answer": "Critical academic text",
      "choices": [
        "Descriptive",
        "Analytical",
        "Persuasive",
        "Critical academic text"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Types of Academic Texts"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the language needed by students to do the work in schools?",
      "answer": "Academic Language",
      "choices": [
        "Social Language",
        "Academic Language",
        "Formal Language",
        "Informal Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Language Types"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the set of vocabulary that allows us to communicate with others in the context of regular daily conversations?",
      "answer": "Social Language",
      "choices": [
        "Academic Language",
        "Social Language",
        "Informal Language",
        "Formal Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Language Types"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the basic structure that is used by an academic text is consist of three (3) parts introduction, body, and conclusion which is formal and logical?",
      "answer": "Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation",
        "Structure"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What enables the reader to follow the argument and navigate the text?",
      "answer": "Structure",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What refers to the attitude conveyed in a piece of writing?",
      "answer": "Tone",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What should be used for the arguments of others to be fairly presented and with an appropriate narrative tone?",
      "answer": "Tone",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Language",
        "Citation"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What enables a reader to follow your line of thinking without difficulty?",
      "answer": "Clear topic sentences",
      "choices": [
        "Unambiguous language",
        "Clear topic sentences",
        "Third person point-of-view",
        "Formal language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a very important aspect of an academic text for citing sources in the body of the paper and providing a list of references as either footnotes or endnotes?",
      "answer": "Citation",
      "choices": [
        "Citation",
        "Structure",
        "Language",
        "Tone"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the starting point of an academic text is a particular perspective, idea or position applied to the chosen research problem?",
      "answer": "Thesis-driven",
      "choices": [
        "Structure",
        "Tone",
        "Thesis-driven",
        "Language"
      ],
      "reference": "L1-ACADEMIC TEXT.pptx",
      "term": "Features of Academic Writing"
    }
  ]
}